emaplan.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy Policy | eMoney

###### 1\. Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is very important to eMoney Advisor, LLC (“ **our** “, “ **we** “, and/or “ **us** “). Because we collect certain types of information about the users of our website found at www.emoneyadvisor.com (the “ **Site** “), we believe you should fully understand the conditions of our collection and use of such information. This privacy policy (this “ **Policy** “) discloses what information we collect, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. By using the Site, you consent to our collection and use of your personally identifiable information as described in this Policy.

This Privacy Policy addresses the following topics:

  * The security precautions we have implemented to protect information we collect;
  * The types of personally identifiable information we collect and how we use it;
  * How we disclose the information we collect; Use of “cookies” and related technologies;
  * Other reasons for sharing information and how we retain information;
  * Links to third party web sites;
  * Your choice and opt-out provisions;
  * How to correct and/or change the information we collect;
  * Modifications to this Policy;
  * Assigning this Policy due to business transactions; and
  * How to contact us.

###### 2\. Security Precautions

We employ various measures to secure your personally identifiable information. The security, integrity and confidentiality of your information are extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures that are designed to protect guest information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use and modification. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. E-mails sent to us are not secure and we make no representation that any data contained in an e-mail sent to us will be secure. Thus, if your communication contains sensitive or confidential information or financial information, you should send it to us via regular mail. Except as otherwise set forth in this Policy, we restrict access to customer data to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you.

###### 3\. Personally identifiable information Collected

In this Policy, “personally identifiable information” means information or an information set that identifies or could be used by or on behalf of eMoney to identify an individual, which may include your name, address, telephone number and other types of data. Except as described in this Policy, eMoney will not give, sell, rent or loan any personally identifiable information to any third party.

Personally identifiable information does not include “ **Usage Data** ” which we define as encoded or anonymized information or aggregated data (such as IP addresses) we collect about a group or category of services, features or users, which does not contain personally identifiable information. Usage Data helps us understand trends in usage of the Site so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor the Site. In addition to collecting and using Usage Data ourselves, we may share Usage Data with third parties, including our customers, partners and service providers, for various purposes, including to help us better understand our customers’ needs and improve the Site as well as for advertising and marketing purposes. We do not share Usage Data with third parties in a way that would enable them to identify you.

If you make a written request via the Site for us to contact you or to subscribe to our online wealth planning system (the “ **System** “), we may use that personally identifiable information you provide in order to contact and communicate with you about the Site and your potential interest in subscribing to our System, send you marketing materials (subject to your opt-out option), for research purposes, and to generally improve the content and functionality of the Site and/or the System. You can choose not to receive future e-mails from eMoney at any time, by contacting our customer service (see Section 9 below). However, to the extent that corrected or deleted information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will immediately reach the other databases. Please note that we may occasionally contact you for administrative purposes even if you unsubscribe from our distribution lists.

We may also share your personally identifiable information with third-party service providers (such as credit card processors and application functionality partners) to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and other services we use to operate the Site and System and maintain a high quality user experience. We do not permit our service providers to use the personally identifiable information you provide for their marketing purposes.

We accept inquiries and applications regarding our open job postings through the Site. This may include resume files. Personally identifiable information submitted by job applicants when applying for a position is only used for the purpose of evaluating the candidate for a position at eMoney and is managed according to our human resources department policies.

###### 4\. Cookies

A “cookie” is a small software file stored temporarily or placed on your computer’s hard drive. The main purpose of a cookie is to allow a web server to identify your computer and web browser, and tailor web pages and/or login information to your preferences. Cookies help us promptly display the information you need to use the capabilities of the Site and other information, which we consider to be of interest to you. By gathering and remembering information about your website preferences through cookies, we can provide a better experience. Cookies don’t give us access to users’ computers, and the information we collect through cookies doesn’t include personally identifiable information.

When you use the Site we utilize “session cookies,” which allow us to uniquely identify your browser while you are logged in and to process your online transactions. Session cookies disappear from your computer when you close your web browser or turn off your computer. We also utilize “persistent cookies” to identify you as an eMoney customer or end user and make it easier for you to log into and use the Site. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your web browser or turn off your computer.

We utilize various categories of cookies, which are summarized below along with the options available to you to manage them.

Essential: Essential cookies are those that are critical to the functionality of the Site. We use these cookies to keep a user logged into the Site and remember relevant information when the user returns to the Site.

Functional: We use functional cookies to track users’ activities in the Site, understand their preferences and improve their user experience. These cookies can also be used to remember configurations of the Site that you can customize.

Marketing: We engage third party providers to serve a variety of marketing cookies that enable us to track and analyze usage, navigational and other statistical information from visitors to the Site. This information does not include personally identifiable information though we may re-associate this information with personally identifiable information we have collected when it is received. Marketing cookies are also used to track the performance of our advertisements and are employed by third party advertising networks that we utilize. These ad networks follow online activities of visitors to the Site and use this information to inform, optimize and serve tailored advertisements on the Site or on other websites you visit that we believe would most effectively promote the Site to you. We also use third parties to collect information that assists us in other methods of “remarketing” our Service to visitors to the Site.

You can generally accept or decline the use of cookies through a functionality built into your web browser. Please note that if you do elect to disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies, you may not be able to access or take advantage of many features of the Site.

If you require more specific information as to the nature of the cookies utilized in the Site for purposes of fulfilling these obligations, please contact us by email at [privacy@emoneyadvisor.com](mailto:privacy@emoneyadvisor.com).

As is true with most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol addresses as well as browser, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We generally use this information as we would any Usage Data, to analyze trends, administer and maintain the Site, or track usage of various features within the Site.

###### 5\. Other Information Sharing; Retention

In addition to the purposes described above, we disclose personally identifiable information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also share such information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. We will retain personally identifiable information we process on behalf of our customers for as long as needed to provide services to our customers, subject to our compliance with this Policy. We may further retain and use this personally identifiable information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

###### 6\. Do Not Track

Because there is not yet a consensus on how companies should respond to web browser-based do-not-track (DNT) mechanisms, we do not respond to any browser-based DNT signals.

###### 7\. Links to Other Websites

The Site may contain links to other websites and web applications that are not owned or controlled by eMoney. Please be aware that we do not determine and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site, and read the privacy statements of other websites and web applications linked to the Site. This Policy applies only to information collected by the Site.

###### 8\. Choice

We process and store information on behalf of our customers. If you would like to opt out of getting communications from eMoney please contact us at [privacy@emoneyadvisor.com](mailto:privacy@emoneyadvisor.com) or follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each marketing email. Requests to opt-out of transfers to our third-party vendors will also be considered, but limitations on data sharing may make it difficult or impossible to provide the Site in this manner.

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83 and 1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personally identifiable information we share with third parties or affiliates for their own direct marketing purposes during the previous calendar year. eMoney does not share personally identifiable information with unrelated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. If you would like a copy of this notice, please refer to the “Contact Us” section at the end of this Policy for appropriate contact information. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice”.

###### 9\. Correcting and Updating Your Information

Users may update or change the personally identifiable information they have provided eMoney by logging into the Site and providing such additional information where applicable. Otherwise, you may contact Customer Service by email: [customerservice@emoneyadvisor.com](mailto:privacy@emoneyadvisor.com) or phone: 1-888-362-8482.

###### 10\. Modifications to This Privacy Policy

We may modify, amend, add or delete the terms of this Policy at any time. If we modify this Policy, we will notify you by postal mail, an email that provides a link to the modified Policy or some other method (such as by placing a conspicuous notice of the new Policy on the web site or by presenting you with a web page containing an electronic copy of the Privacy Policy) that provides fair notice of the promulgation of the modified Policy. Your only remedy, if you do not accept the terms of this Policy, is to discontinue use of the Site.

###### 11\. Business Transactions

We may assign or transfer this Policy, and your user account and related information and data, including any personally identifiable information, to any person or entity that acquires all or substantially all of the business, stock or assets of, or is merged with eMoney.

###### 12\. Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or about the privacy practices of eMoney, please contact us by email at [privacy@emoneyadvisor.com](mailto:privacy@emoneyadvisor.com) using the subject title of “Privacy Policy”, by phone at 1-888-362-8482 (and mention that you have a Privacy Policy question related to the Corporate Site) or by mail to:

**Attn: Privacy Officer**  
eMoney Advisor, LLC  
Four Radnor Corporate Center, Suite 300  
100 Matsonford Road  
Radnor, PA 19087
